Guide to the Time Inc. The March of Time Records 1935-1995 MS 3009-RG 15
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1979-1995, undated; 12.5 Linear Feet (13 boxes)
  - Subseries IV.A. Internal Use, 1979-1995, undated; 11 Linear Feet (11 boxes)
    - March of Time: Vol. 2 Issues 6-7, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 2 #6 Vol 2 #7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 2 Issues 6-7, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 2 #6/7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 2 Issue 8 and Vol. 3 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 2 # 8 Vol 3 #1 Vol 3 #2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 2 Issue 8 and Vol. 3 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 2 # 8 Vol 3 # 1 Vol 3 #2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issues 3-4, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 3 #3 Vol 3 #4"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issues 3-4, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 16)
      1 videocasette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 3 #3 Vol 3 #4"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issues 5-7, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 17)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol #3 Episode #5, 6, and 7". Includes a note: "Vol. III Issue #5 THE FAR EAST (CHINA'S DICTATOR KIDNAPPED) Dec. 1936"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issues 5-7, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. Label on case is ripped, label on the videocassette states: "March of Time Vol #3 Episode #5, 6, and 7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issue 7, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 3 #7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issue 7, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 3 #7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issues 8-9, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 3 #8/9"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issues 8-9, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 3 #8 Vol 3 #9"
    - March of Time: Vol. 3 Issues 12-13, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #3 Episode #12 and 13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 2-3, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #4 Episode #2 and 3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 2-3, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #4 Episode #2 and 3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 4-6, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #4 Episode #4, 5, and 6"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 4-6, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #4 Episode #4, 5, and 6"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 7-8, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: March of Time Vol 4 #7/8". Includes a note: "Vol. IV issue #8 ARMS AND THE LEAGUE March 1938"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 7-8, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 4 #7 Vol 4 #8". Includes a note: "TAPE BROKEN"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issue 9 and Vol. 8 Issue 13, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #4 Episode #9 Volume #8 Episode #13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issue 9 and Vol. 8 Issue 13, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #4 Episode #9 Volume #8 Episode #13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 10-11, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 4 #10/11"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 10-11, undated (Offsite-box 2800, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 4 #10 Vol 4 #11"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 12-13, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #4 Episode #12 and 13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 12-13, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 4 #12/13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 4 Issues 12-13, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 4 #12 Vol 4 #13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 5 #1/2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 5 #1 Vol 5 #2".
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 5-6, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #5 Episode #5 and 6"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 5-6, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #5 Episode #5 and 6"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 7-8, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #5 Episode #7 and 8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 7-8, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-Matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #5 Episode #7 and 8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 9-10, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #5 Episode #9 and 10"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 9-10, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: " March of Time Volume #5 Episode #9 and 10"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 11-12, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 5 EP 11/12"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 12-13 and Vol. 6 Issue 1, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #5 Episode #12 and 13 Volume #6 Episode #1"
    - March of Time: Vol. 5 Issues 12-13 and Vol. 6 Issue 1, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #5 Episode #12 and 13 Volume #6 Episode #1"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issues 2-3, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 6 #2 Vol 6 #3"
    - March of Time: Vol 6 Issues 2-3, undated (Offsite-box 2801, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 6 #2 Vol 6 #3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issues 4-5, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #6 Episode #4 and 5"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issue 6, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 6 #6"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issue 6, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 6 #6"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issue 7, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 6 #7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issue 7, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 6 #7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issues 8-9, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #6 Episode #8 and 9"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issues 8-9, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #6 Episode #8 and 9"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issues 10-11, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #6 Episode #10 and 11"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issues 10-11, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #6 Episode #10 and 11"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issues 11-13, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #6 Episode #11, 12, and 13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 6 Issues 11-13, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #6 Episode #11, 12, and 13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #1 and 2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #1 and 2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 3-4, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #3 and 4"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 3-4, undated (Offsite-box 2802, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #3 and 4"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 5-6, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #5 and 6"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 7-9, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #7, 8, and 9"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 7-9, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #7, 8, and 9"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 9-10, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 7 EP 9/10"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 11-12, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume#7 Episode #11 and 12". Includes a note: "Vol. VII issue #11 CHINA FIGHTS BACK June 1941"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issues 11-12, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #11 and 12"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issue 13 and Vol. 8 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #7 Episode #13 Volume #8 Episode #1 annd 2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issue 13 and Vol. 8 Issue 7, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #8 Episode #7 Volume #7 Episode #13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 7 Issue 13 and Vol. 8 Issue 7, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #8 Episode #7 Volume #7 Episode 13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 8 Issues 3-5, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #8 Episode #3, 4, and 5"
    - March of Time: Vol. 8 Issues 6 and 8, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #8 Episode #6 Volume #8 Episode #8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 8 Issues 6 and 8, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #8 Episode #6 Volume #8 Episode #8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 8 Issues 9 and 11, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #8 Episode #9 and 11"
    - March of Time: Vol. 8 Issues 12-13 and Vol. 9 Issue 1, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #8 Episode #12 and 13 Volume #9 Episode #1"
    - March of Time: Vol. 8 Issues 12-13 and Vol. 9 Issue 1, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #8 Episode #12 and 13 Volume #9 Episode #1"
    - March of Time: Vol. 9 Issue 2-4, undated (Offsite-box 2803, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #9 Episode #2, 3, and 4"
    - March of Time: Vol. 9 Issue 2-4, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #9 Episode #2, 3, and 4"
    - March of Time: Vol 9 Issue 8 and Vol. 10 Issue 4, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #4 Volume #9 Episode #8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 9 Issue 8 and Vol. 10 Issue 4, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #4 Volume #9 Episode #8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 9 Issue 10-11, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on front of case and cassette: "March of Time Vol 9 EP 11/10". Label on side of case: "114. March of TIME 111/10/92 Vol 9 NOS?"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issue 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #1 and 2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issue 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #1 and 2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issue 3 and 8, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #3 and 8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issues 3 and 8, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #3 and 8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issues 5 and 7, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 10 #5 Vol 10 #7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issues 5 and 7, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label:"March of Time Vol 10 #5 Vol 10 #7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issues 6 and 10, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #6 Volume #10 Episode #10"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issues 6 and 10, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #6 Volume #10 Episode #10"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issues 12-13, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #12 and 13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 10 Issues 12-13, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #10 Episode #12 and 13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issues 1 and 3, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #1 and 3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issues 1 and 3, undated (Offsite-box 2804, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #1 and 3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issue 2 and Vol. 13 Issue 1, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #2 Volume 13 Episode #1"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issue 2 and Vol. 13 Issue 1, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume 11 Episode #2 Volume #13 Episdoe #1"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issues 4-5, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #4 and 5"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issue 4-5, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #4 and 5"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issues 6-7, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label: "(dup March of Time Vol 11 EP 6/7". On cassette label: "March of Time Vol 11 Ep 6/7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issue 8 and Vol 12 Issue 3, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On front case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 11 Episode #8 Vol 12 Episode #3". On label on side of case: "95. March of TIME Vol. 11, Ep. 8 Vol 12, Ep. 3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issue 8 and Vol. 12 Issue 3, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 11 Episode #8 Vol 12 Episode #3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issues 9-10, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #9 and 10"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issues 9-10, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #9 and 10"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issues 11-12, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #11 and 12"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issues 11-12, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #11 Episode #11 and 12"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issue 13 and Vol. 12 Issue 1, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On front case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 11 Episode #13 Vol 12 Episode #1". On label on side of case: "90. March of Time Vol. 11 and 12"
    - March of Time: Vol. 11 Issue 13 and Vol. 12 Issue 1, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 11 Episode #13 Vol 12 Episode #1"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issues 2 and 8, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 12 #2/8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issues 4-5, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On front case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 12 Episode #4 and 5". On side case label: "101. March of TIME Vol. 12, E4,5"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issues 4-5, undated (Offsite-box 2805, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 12 Episode #4 and 5"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issue 7 and Vol. 13 Issue 4, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On front case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 12 Episode #7 Vol 13 Episode #4". On side case label: "94. March of TIME Vol 12, Ep. 7 Vol 13, Ep.4"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issue 7 and Vol. 13 Issue 4, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 12 Episode #7 Vol 13 Episode #4"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issues 9 and 11, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 12 #9 Vol 12 #11"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issues 9 and 11, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-Matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 12 #9 Vol 12 #11"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issues 10 and 12, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 12 EP 10/12"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issue 13 and Vol. 15 Issues 2-3, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #15 Episode #2 and 3 Volume #12 Episode #13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 12 Issue 13 and Vol. 15 Issues 2-3, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #15 Episode #2 and 3 Volume #12 Episode #13"
    - March of Time: Vol. 13 Issues 2-3, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On front case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 13 Episode #2 and 3". On side case label: "100. March of TIME Vol. 13, E. 2, 3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 13 Issues 2-3, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 13 Episode #2 and 3"
    - March of Time: Vol. 13 Issues 6-7, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #13 Episode #6 and 7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 13 Issues 6-7, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On front case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 13 Episode #6 and 7". On side case label: "98. March of TIME Vol. 13, E. 6,7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 13 Issues 6-7, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #13 Episode #6 and 7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 13 Issues 8 and 10, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #13 Episode #8 and 10"
    - March of Time: Vol. 13 Issues 8 and 10, undated (Offsite-box 2806, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On front case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 13 Episode #8 and 10". On side case label: "93. March of TIME Vol. 13, Ep. 8 and 10"